Joyner
是啊我离升有段时向了但现在我又回来了
Yeah, it's been a minutes, but Im back in it (Uh)
和你们交手的不再是从前那个人
Yall ain't dealing with the same boy (No)
稍稍飞嗨一点再开始我的转型
Got a little trippy, then I transitioned (Yeah)
全新的思路加上纯摔的很货
New attitude mixed with that pure raw (Aw)
夜唤游戏时向你家妞来了电话
The night game, your girl called
她说“来吧宝贝来忙活忙活”
She like, "Do me, baby, down to get busy, busy?" (Yes)
不玩骰子好好爽爽
No dice, chill, whoadie (No)
迷迷糊糊 过着日子
In life, feeling dizzy
晨光初现城市蒙胧我就投身战争
Oh, having visions of the city and I go to war
我的身影从白天忙碌到深夜
See me in the day through the late night (Night)
告诉他们这就是我的魔法高她不胜寒
Tell 'em it's the charm, I'm in freeze mode
直冲神境英雄一旦起飞就无人能挡
To the gods, can't stop a hero when he in flight (Flight)
我在光明中畅游
I'm swimming in the light right
给你搞些来给他们秀秀看这是全新的我
Go and get you some, go and show 'em something, this a new thang
对我的蛋蛋放任自由
Yeah, Ilet my nuts hang (Yeah)
像詹姆斯和丰德在你头上暴扣
Knock your top off with LeBron or Dwyane Wade (Yeah)
原地起飞
Aww, lift off
别想阻拦我的发展快滚蛋边果着去
Can't stunt a nigga growth, better get gone, move along (Uh)
你可不想崩溃吧要试试吗？
You don't wanna trip, wanna get it on (Uh)
你根本不想搞事可别误会了
You don't wanna act, don't get me wrong (Nah)
人们根本不认真听歌词
They don't Tisten to the words in the song (Uh-huh)
但我也不会告诉他们先准备起来
We ain't gotta tell 'em we just getting ready (Yeah)
他们装模作样我可不开玩笑
See 'em fronting, we ain't kidding
想要搞事 那我奉陪
If you want it, you can get it
怒火的成员都来试一试
Members of the rage, come and get you some
在飞机上舒舒服服躺下到了地方再离升
Next step's out the jet from the lean back
环游全世界也没有人团观
Running y 'round the world and we ain't packed
一脚油门 嗡嗡开走把人们甩在身后哦这你干过？
Hit 'em, vroom, vroom, leave 'em stuck, oh, you seen that?
和兄弟们在一起快活的时候
Im chillin' where the team at
看一辆黑色奔驰带着家伙停到面前好这些我要了
See a black Benz pull up with some jawns, yeah, I need that
太疯狂了 简直不敢相信
So crazy, can't believe it
不拿相机靠这不是为了上镜说的都是大实话
No cams, damn, no filming at all, real nigga facts (Come on)
几年以前开始接受治疗
Years ago, rehab
非常不错帮我开拓了全新的视野
All good, helped me figure out another plan
在那之前我状态很差非常差
It got bad, so bad
我一点也不喜欢当时的样子
Nah, I ain't fucking love that, man
然后我投着LV包跳进了全新的地域
Then I hopped out in a new zone with my Louis bag
真实的经历带你穿过黑夜与白昼
True story, take you through the dark and the light (Yeah)
上帝之子全新出炉
Godson, got through new
重回世向又是普通的一天
Back up in the world, it's the day in the life (Cud)
点支叶子再次开始
Hit the blunt and get it (Dude)
提高了标准还是同一首歌我们成功了
Raised bars (Uh), same song, we did it (Yeah)
热单配料每一首歌都加满不加审核
Hot sauce, pour it on all jams, explicit
继续前行全力出击 你家妞也陪我一起
Carry on, smoke strong, got your mama down with it (Come on)
圈子里正缺些报货
And the game fuckin' needed something dirty raw
让他们见识下王法我们斩草除根
Tell them this the law and we weeded (Uh)
如果你信仰的是上帝
So if it's God you believe in (Yeah)
那就低下头来点头认可
Bob your head and just nod in agreement (Yeah)
人们总说时向无人能敌
They say time's undefeated
那我就第一个匹敌
I'ma be the first one who can beat it (Yeah)
曾经梦想投篮现在我投着主分
I had hoop dreams, now shoot threes (What?)
赚了点钱那不是叶子的绿
Got a lil'green (Yeah), but I don't do weed (Nope)
也不是紫水糖浆那些是Tunechi专属
Purp nor lean (Nah), that's Tunechi (Yeah)
这才是新奥尔良去他妈的DrewBrees
That's New Orleans (What?) fuck Drew Brees (Yeah)
这才是新奥尔良去他妈的D
还有5nnop Do= 他那有两个6
还有5n00pD0-他那有两个6
Snoop D-O-double (Uh), that's two G's (Yup)
这k我都用来买纸ohh-wee!
probably spent on paper, ooh-wee
从周二开始我飞的叶子倒了几棵树
Since Tuesday, probably killed a few trees (Yeah)
但是我只抽那些松散的叶
But the only ones I smoke are the loose leaf
就算没抽嗨你也得尊称我陛下
Not high, but I'm your highness (What?)
背地里舔我舔的不行
And secretly, you're on my dick (Hah)
你们这些黑粉怕是得屁股疼一群人酸得一匹
But you haters are butthurt (Ow), bunch of sore hind-ends (0w)
我就是个究白小子
I was just a poor white kid (Yeah)
说唱要是篮球我就是乔丹
Now if rap was B-ball, Pd be Jordan-like, bitch (What?)
你做梦都想像我这么得分
You wish you could score like this (Nah), yeah
就算在半场三分我也都进
Not even at half court, I'd miss (Nah)
我就像是漱口水只要在场上投的都是空心
I'm mouthwash, 'cause if I was on the floor, I'd swish (Fluoride, fluoride, swish)
但有一件事骗不了你
But I cannot lie (Nah)
我心目中前五有你
I got you in my top five
是倒数前五
Worst rappers of all time (Hah)
说我跌落神坛你们怕是阿尔茨海默
Ilost my spot, y'all got Alzheim' (Uh)
说唱之王？别是他们说的我可没说
King of rap? Nah, their words, not mine (Yeah)
我是脏话之王这可不是撒谎
King of swear words and not lying (Yeah)
可别和我比
You should never compare yours (Nope)
你就是个热线电话只有这样你才能火
A toll-free number (Yeah), only way you'll ever have a hot line
这他妈是怎么了？
Fuck'sgoing on, man? (Yeah)
上面都是一群蠢蛋
Bunch of half-wits up in office (What?)
半的人在街上游荡如同僵尸末日的场景
Half of us walking around like a zombie apocalypse
另外一半谁也不管
Other half are just pissed off and (Yeah)
不戴口罩还不以为然
Don't wanna wear a mask and they're just scoffing
就是这样你也得了他们那个病
And that's how you end up catching the shit off'em
我刚用过了你的购物篮
I just used the same basket as you shopping
现在我他妈因为你咳嗽进了棺材
Now I'm in a fuckin'casket from you coughin' (Damn)
总是领先黑子一步让他们黑吧
Always stay ahead of haters, let 'em hate
但千万别让叛徒进到你的圈子里
But never let a traitor  penetrate your circle
拖你后腿的人要尽量远离
Separate yourself from those who try to pull you down
真懂的人不会迷失就像美杜莎一样
The real ones never stray, it's sort of like Medusa (Yeah)
只有这样你才能一脑袋蛇
That's how you stay ahead of snakes (Woo)
群歌手天天掏枪我才不管你们多全副武装
Emcees pull out gats, I don't give a fuck how strapped
想要说唱比我强？这我表示杯疑
Youre gonna out-rap me? I doubt that
拜托埃我就像只家鼠
Please, bitch, Im a house rat
说唱对我未说就像捕鼠央上的奶酪
These raps are 'bout that cheese like mousetraps
地球生物我已经习惯他们了
Earthlings, I adapt to 'em
有些事情我不想做
Certain things, I don't want to do, but have to in
但是为了装成人类也只好做一做
Order to just act human
像是在厕所蹲坑用用吸尘器
Like using a bathroom and vacuuming (Yeah)
穿着鹅绒大衣套上生化服在录音室里录歌
Rapping in the booth in a triple fat goose hazmat suit
用泡泡纸裹上几层再戴个口罩
Bubble wrap and a mask too and
这怕不是他们说的“陷阱音乐”
I don't think that's what they meant by trap music (Nah)
在纸墨中穿梭像是在纹身
Running through ink like Im tattooing (Yeah)
这首歌被你们爱的那位屠杀
This is music to be murdered by, you love
调大音量 我就像支烟一样燃起米 OLUME
Turn the volume up, I am fired up like a blunt
调大音量 我就像支烟一样燃起来
赚的钱厚的好似意大利卷我就是拉药
Bread is long like an Italian sub, I am drugs
所以才会收到你们那些嗑嗨了的评价
That is probably why your opinion of me's high as fuck
怒火永不停歇
And it's nonstop fury (Yeah)
因为我不会再阻栏
Cause I ain't holding 'em up like an armed robbery (Nah)
上帝为我陪审就算死去我也不会担心
And God's my jury, so when I die, I'm not worried (Nah)
Floyd和Ahmaud Arbery祈祷
Prayers to George Floyd and Ahmaud Arbery (Yeah)
怎么他妈有那么多黑条子？
How the fuck is it that so many cops are dirty? (Huh?)
停手吧拜托了 警官真对不起
Stop, man, please, officer, I'm sorry
但是你在我身企我喘不过气
But I can't breathe:when I got you on top of me
你他妈膝盖压进我颈动脉了
Your goddamn knee's on my carotid artery (Fuck)
Moon Man和5lim的冒险
The adventures of Moon Man & Slim (Ah)
谁想和他们一起？
Yes, who want it with them?
三部曲续写
The trilogy continues
给你们加餐看看菜单上有什么？
Serving niggas, yes, see what's on the menu (Yeah)
看着人们惊恐万分可真是牛
Watch 'em panfc,hot damnit (Let's get it, baby)
希望你们这些人能看懂
Hope you fuckers understand it
对你们来说太real了
The realer for you niggas
未接受圣典的启示吧
Come and get these scriptures (Yeah)
Rap God (Uh) Rager